Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Dear Sir (1924) lyrics by Howard Dietz, original title Vanity Fair appears on some scores
      - O.S. to G.T., Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Seven days: #14, Parts (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Terzetto See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Robert Bennett) full score in ink, corrections in pencil; 11 p.; Includes: "If you think it's love, you're right" (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Terzett[o]: [If you think it's love] you're right! See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Holograph piano score/sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Terzetto: #'s 20, 15 See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Parts (Box-folder 17/3)
      - There's lots of room for me see: Lots of room for me
      - Valse brillante, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in pencil; 8 p. (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Valse brillante, Parts (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Weeping willow tree: canzonetta: #16 See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 19 p.; Uniform title: Weeping willow tree (Box-folder 12/5)
      - End of canzonetta; Modulation See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Weeping willow tree (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Weeping willow tree: canzonetta See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Ms. (Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p. (incomplete; 6 3/4" x 10") (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Weeping willow tree: act II scene I See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Carbon of typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Weeping willow tree See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil; 9 p. (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Weeping willow tree: canzonetta See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in Kern's hand in pencil, no lyric; 9 p.; Note: once titled "Caprice"; appears to have been written prior to Dear Sir (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Weeping willow tree: Canzonetta: #16 See also: Caprice in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, some annotations in Kern's hand in pencil, partial lyric in pencil; 9 p. (Box-folder 12/22)
      - What's the use: #3, Parts (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Wishing well scene see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - [Unidentified], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 17-26; Note: corresponds to middle section of "Genevieve and men" (box 12, folder 11) (Box-folder 12/6)
      - [Unidentified], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 13-17 + [2]; Note: p. 13-17 corresponds to "New finale act I" sketch (box 12, folder 17) (Box-folder 12/7)
      - [Unidentified holograph sketches]: Verse, Holograph [?] sketch in pencil; 2 p.; On back: sketch in pencil, melody only (Box-folder 12/23)
      - [Unidentified holograph sketches]: Song, Holograph sketch in pencil; 1 p. (7" x 5.5") (Box-folder 12/23)
      - [Untitled], Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/23)
      - [Untitled], Holograph sketch in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 12/23)
      - [Untitled], Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) short score/sketch in pencil; p. A-E (6 3/4" x 10"); Includes: "Oscar's entrance (new)" "I want to be there" (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Allegretto, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 4 p. (Box-folder 12/24)
      - [Untitled], Ms. harmonic sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 12/24)
      - [Miscellaneous/unidentified], Parts (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Doll Girl (1913)
      - If we were on our honeymoon (railway duet) see: Magnolia and Julie from Show Boat
      - A little thing like a kiss: Act I, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, 2nd lyric line in pencil; 4 p.; Lyric by Harry B. Smith (Box-folder 18/1)
      - When three is company: Cupid song, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [3] p.; Lyric by M. E. Rourke (Box-folder 18/2)
    - The Fallen Angel
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - The Flame Within
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Fluffy Ruffles (1908)
      - Won't you let me carry your parcel?: quartette, Typed lyric sheet with annotations in pencil; 2 p.; Lyric by C. H. Bovill (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Gentlemen Unafraid
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - The Girl from Utah (1914) lyrics by Harry B. Smith
      - The land of "let's pretend", Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (incomplete); Photocopy of above; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/4)
      - We'll take care of you, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 18/5)
      - Why don't they dance the polka, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p.; On back: Kern notes and sketch in pencil; Mimeograph of typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/6)
      - A medley of interpolated songs from The Girl From Utah, Printed piano score, with ms. pasteovers in ink on p. 7 and the bottom of p. 8; 8 p.; Includes: "The land of lets pretend" "The girl in the clogs and the shawl" "You never can tell" "They didn't believe me" "The same sort of girl" "Why don't they dance the polka" [Unidentified/incomplete music] (Box-folder 18/7)
      - Medley of songs by Jerome Kern introduced in The Girl From Utah, Parts, 2 sets, 1 printed set and 1 ms. in ink; Includes: "Why don't they dance the polka" "The girl in the clogs and shawl" "The land of 'let's pretend'" "Florrie the flapper" "They didn't believe me" "Same sort of girl" "You never can tell" "Gilbert the Filbert" (by Herman Finck) (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Good Morning, Dearie (1921) Lyrics by Anne Caldwell
      - Act II scene II, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 9 p.; Note: this number became "Good morning, dearie" (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Dance, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score/short score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Dance eccentrique, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Easy pickin's, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Entr'acte, Printed (cut and paste) and ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score/short score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Entrance of sailors: Entrance of sailors, scene music and blues, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil; 26 p. (Box-folder 18/14)
      - [Entrance of sailors: cut material], Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; p. 13-27 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Finale, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Finale act I, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p. (+ pasteover inserts on back of 2 p.) (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Good morning dearie, Carbon of typed lyric sheet; p. 13; Includes original lyric of "Rosy Ruby" (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Introduction act I: Opening chorus, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Kalua, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 18/19)
      - Machine music, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p.; Note: butterfly symbol in top left corner means once intended for Love o' Mike; Uniform title: Machine music (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Melican papa, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Niagara falls, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (incomplete); Typed lyric sheet; p. 11 (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Niagara falls: dance, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Niagara falls, Printed piano-vocal score (p. 1-7), and ms. (Stephen O. Jones) emendations & coda in ink (p. 8-10); 10 p. (Box-folder 114/10)
      - Opening act I: Opening chorus, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Opening chorus, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink; 13 p.; Includes: "My lady's dress" (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Opening scene II act II and song, Ms. (Stephen Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil, no lyric; 9 p. (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Overture, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Pas de deux, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Prelude/Vorspiel act II, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Sing song girl: scene II act I, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Toddle, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Way down town, Ms. (Stephen O. Jones) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 6 p.; Carbon of typed lyric sheet laid in; p. 2 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Have a Heart (1917) lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse & Jerome Kern
      - And I am all alone, Printed piano-vocal score; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Have a heart: duet: Peggy & Owen: no. 5b, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p. (Box-folder 19/8)
      - I'm here, little girls, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 19/9)
      - Peter Pan, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 19/10)
      - The road that lies [before], Parts (on piano part: "arr. by Charles N. Grant") (Box-folder 19/11)
      - You can't keep a good man down: no. 2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; [6] p. (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Hayfoot, Strawfoot
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Head Over Heels (1918) lyrics by Jerome Kern & Edgar Allan Woolf
      - The charity bazaar see: Opening act two
      - Calliope see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Come now, smile, houpla!: Laughter: no. 10, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 7 p. (Box-folder 19/13)
      - Finale act I: no. 13, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 20 p. (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Frieda's lullaby: no. 4, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Houp-la see: Come now, smile, houpla!
      - Ladies, have a care! see: Trio male
      - Let us build a little nest See also: "Let us build a little nest" from The Polish Wedding, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Let us build a little nest See also: "Let us build a little nest" from The Polish Wedding, 1st proof for printed piano-vocal score, annotated; p. 2 only (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Me see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Mitzi's lullaby see: Frieda's lullaby
      - Opening: no. 1, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 13 p. (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Opening act two: #14, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 13 p. (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Opening act II addenda, Holograph sketch in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Spring: no. 2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 10 p. (Box-folder 19/19)
      - Today is spring see: Spring
      - Trio male: no. 16, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 7 p. (Box-folder 19/20)
      - Worderveele show: I could almost do vaudvill, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [4] p.; Carbon of typed lyric sheet; p. 7; Uniform title: Vorderveele (Box-folder 19/21)
      - With type a-ticking see: Opening
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets; [9] p.; Includes: [Come now, smile, houpla!]: Smile [Finale act I]: Finale 1 Ladies have a care Opening act II: [The charity bazaar] [Today is spring]: We've brought spring into the room [Vorderveele] [With type a-ticking]: Opening chorus (Box-folder 19/22)
    - High, Wide and Handsome
      - [Various titles] see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
    - Hitchy Koo (1920) lyrics by Anne Caldwell & Glen MacDonough
      - Bring 'em back, Parts (ms.) (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Bring 'em back, Parts (printed, orch. by Robert Russell Bennett) (Box-folder 19/24)
      - A wee little teeny bit, Arranger's holograph (Saddler) full score in ink, annotations in pencil; 10 p. (Box-folder 19/25)
      - You stole away my heart, or, A wee little teeny bit, Carbon of typed lyric sheet [1] p.; Note: this number was probably intended for She's a Good Fellow (Box-folder 19/25)
      - A wee little teeny bit, Parts (Box-folder 19/26)
    - The Kiss Waltz (1911) lyrics by Matthew Woodward
      - Love's charming art (in a lesson or two): the dove duet: act II, Ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [3] p.; Carbon of typed lyric sheet, annotations in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 19/27)
    - The Laughing Husband (1914) lyrics by Harry B. Smith
      - Love is like a violin, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score with violin solo, in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 19/28)
      - Take a step with me, Printed piano-vocal score for "Rosalie" (from the 1906 show The Spring Chicken, with lyrics by George Grossmith, Jr.), annotations and new lyric in Kern's hand in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 19/29)
    - Leave It to Jane (1917) lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse
      - Cleopatterer, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 20/1)
      - The crickets are calling: #7, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 20/2)
      - Duet, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Duet, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 3 p. (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Duet for you: #14, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Finale act I: #12, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 32 p. + 2nd p. 3 after p. 13; Includes: "Leave it to Jane" "What I'm longing to say" "Tomorrow" "Goodnight ladies" "The crickets are calling" (Box-folder 20/5)
      - For you, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 20/6)
      - I don't care: #17, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 20/7)
      - I don't care: #17, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 20/8)
      - I don't care: #17, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 20/8)
      - I'm going to find a girl, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 20/9)
      - It's a great big land: #11, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 20/10)
      - I've had my share see: I don't care
      - [Just you watch my step]: #'s 4a-4b, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Leave it to Jane: #6 See also: Whistling Dan from Ninety in the Shade, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 13 p. (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Opening act I: #1, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Opening act I, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Opening act II: #13, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 26 p. (Box-folder 20/15)
      - A peach of a life!: #2, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 20/16)
      - A peach of a life!: #2, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 20/17)
      - Poor prune, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 20/18)
      - Sir Gallahad [sic]: #15, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 20/19)
      - Sir Galahad, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 5 p.; On back: ms. sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 20/20)
      - The sun shines brighter: #18, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 20/21)
      - To-morrow, maybe!: #3, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 20/22)
      - Wait till tomorrow see: Tomorrow, maybe!
      - What I'm longing to say see: Duet
      - When your favorite girl's not there: #10, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 14 p., + extra p. 4 (unrelated) (Box-folder 20/23)
      - There it is again, or, When your favorite girl's not there, Ms. piano score in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: When your favorite girl's not there (Box-folder 20/24)
      - Why?: #5, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 20/25)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed or typed carbon lyric sheets, some with annotations in ink or pencil, some in Kern's hand; [14] p.; Includes: [The crickets are calling]: 6: Duet: Billy & Jane Football song [I don't care or I've had my share]: Song: Billy and girls [It's a great big land]: Duet: Billy & Jane [I've played for you]: Duet: Billy & Jane: act two 1: Opening: Atwater college song [A peach of a life]: 2: Duet: Stub and Bessie [Poor prune]: 5: Song: Flora Wiggins [Sir Galahad]: Trio: Bub. McGowan & Flora [The Siren's song]: Song: Jane & girls: act two [The sun shines brighter]: Duet: Stub & Bessie [There it is again]: Duet: Billy and Sally [Wait till tomorrow]: 3: Song: Jane & boys What I'm longing to say: duet -- Jane and Bobby: act 1, scene 2 [Why?]: 4 Duet: Flora & McGowan (Box-folder 20/26)
    - Lieber Augustin (1913) lyric by M.E. Rourke (the show was later titled Miss Caprice)
      - Look in her eyes!, Holograph piano-vocal score in ink and pencil; 6 p.; On back: holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Mimeograph of typed lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Love o' Mike (1917) lyrics by Harry B. Smith
      - Don't forget see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Don't tempt me!: no. 6, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 15 p. (Box-folder 21/2)
      - Human after all see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - I wonder why: no. 9, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 21/3)
      - It wasn't my fault: #4, Arranger's holograph (Charles Miller) full score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 21/4)
      - [It wasn't my] fault, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 21/5)
      - Italy, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; [2] p.; On t.p.: "Refrain for 'Simple little tune'" (Box-folder 21/6)
      - Simple little tune, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 21/7)
      - We'll see, Parts (incomplete) (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Lucky (1927) by Otto Harbach, Bert Kalmar, Harry Ruby and Jerome Kern
      - Ballet, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 53 p.; Music by Jerome Kern and Harry Ruby (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Ballet, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; 9 p; On back: ms. sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Ballet, Copyist's ms. piano score in ink; 1 p. (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Bo-tree, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 10 p.; Note: instructional note laid in (Box-folder 21/10)
      - Bow tree [sic], Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 23/9)
      - The bo-tree, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p.; Typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Bo-tree, Parts (Box-folder 23/29)
      - *Buddha, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p.; Music by Harry Ruby (Box-folder 21/11)
      - *By the light of the silvery moon, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; [12] p. + p. 9.5 in Bennet's hand; Music by Gus Edwards (Box-folder 21/12)
      - Cingalese village: opening: #1, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; 10 p.; Includes: "The treasure hunt" by Kalmar and Ruby and Kern (Box-folder 23/10)
      - *Clair de lune, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; 3 p.; Music attributed incorrectly to Kern (Box-folder 21/13)
      - *Clair de lune, Copyist's ms. full score in ink; 4 p.; Music attributed incorrectly to Kern (Box-folder 21/13)
      - Cocoanut dance See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 21/14)
      - Cocoanut dance: rasch ballet See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 23/11)
      - End of Whiteman act and introduction to ballet, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in ink; 4 p.; Includes: "That certain something" "Bo tree" (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Entrance of Lucky, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 29 p. (Box-folder 21/15)
      - Finale act one See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-5, 7-15, 19-23, 28-33, 38-42; Note: see "New finale act I" for missing pages; Music by Harry Ruby and Jerome Kern (Box-folder 21/16)
      - Finale act I: #12a See also: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink, partial lyric in pencil; 11 p. (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Finaletto, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 23 p.; Note: no p. 21 because of mis-numbering; Music by Jerome Kern and Harry Ruby (Box-folder 21/17)
      - Finaletto scene I act I: #7, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations by Kern; 12 p.; By Kalmar and Ruby and Kern; Note: p. 1 water damaged (Box-folder 23/14)
      - from "Bo tree" to "Once in a blue moon" [segue], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 22/1)
      - *I'm no good without you, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 6 p. (p. 3-4 missing); By Kalmar and Ruby (Box-folder 23/15)
      - Intro to ballet, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 17 p. + [1] p. laid in (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Introduction to ballet: jazz band arr., Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 15 p.; Note: for Paul Whiteman's band (Box-folder 22/3)
      - Lucky: refrain, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 23/16)
      - Mendicants, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 3 p.; Note: corresponds to beginning of "Finale act I" piano-vocal score (Box-folder 23/17)
      - Moment sérieux: finale act I, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; 8 p. (Box-folder 23/18)
      - *My sweetheart's the man in the moon: #5, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 15 p.; Music by James Thornton (Box-folder 22/4)
      - New finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-16, 7-13, 17-18, 18, 24-27, 34-36, 19-20, 37, 6, 21, 16-17, 22-29; Music by Jerome Kern and Harry Ruby; Note: includes missing pages from "Finale act one" (Box-folder 22/5)
      - New moon dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p.; Based on Harry Ruby's "The same old moon" (Box-folder 22/6)
      - Once in a blue moon, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Once in a blue moon, Printed piano-vocal score from Stepping Stones, with lyrics by Anne Caldwell; 5 p. (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Opening, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 129 p.; Music by Harry Ruby and Jerome Kern; Includes: "Cingalese village" "The treasure hunt" (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Opening act two, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 46 p. (Box-folder 22/9)